Aveontae M. Frazier

7501 W 61st Apt 133 Mission, KS 66202. (860) 879-1451 amfrazier01@gmail.com

SUMMARY

INFORMATION SYSTEMS AND CODING BOOTCAMP STUDENT WITH EXPERIENCE AND EXTENSIVE EDUCATION IN SOFTWARE DESIGN AND APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT. STRONG WORK ETHIC IN TEAM OR INDIVIDUAL SETTINGS TO DRIVE PRODUCT SUCCESS AND PROCESS EFFICIENCY, STRONG TROUBLESHOOTING AND PROBLEM-SOLVING SKILLS WITH AN ANALYTICAL MINDSET. INTERN INVESTIGATOR WORKING TO ENSURE MAXIMUM COMPLIANCE WITH THE EMPLOYEE RETIREMENT INCOME SECURITY ACT OF 1974 (ERISA) AND CRIMINAL PROVISIONS OF THE U.S. CODE AS THEY RELATE TO EMPLOYEE BENEFIT PLANS.

KNOWLEDGE, SKILLS, AND ABILITIES

- KNOWLEDGE OF FUNDAMENTAL CONCEPTS OF WEB DEVELOPMENT, INCLUDING HTML, CSS, AND JAVASCRIPT.
- ABILITY TO WORK WITH SERVERS, DATABASES, AND OTHER BACK-END TECHNOLOGIES, SUCH AS MYSOL DATABASE, NODE, JS. EXPRESS, JS. AND
- SKILLED IN TROUBLESHOOTING CODE RELATED ISSUES/DEFECTS.
- ABILITY TO BUILD A CLIENT-SIDE APPLICATION USING THIRD-PARTY API'S.
- KNOWLEDGEABLE IN TROUBLESHOOTING BASIC SOFTWARE ISSUES.
- SKILLED IN CONDUCTING RESEARCH, COLLECTING AND DEVELOPING DATA REPORTS ON ENFORCEMENT PROGRAM, ADMINISTRATIVE OPERATIONS, AND ACCOMPLISHMENTS OF THE OFFICE
- KNOWLEDGE OF CONDUCTING INVESTIGATIONS, INCLUDING ANALYSIS AND GATHERING OF EVIDENCE AND USE OF INVESTIGATIVE TECHNIQUES

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF KANSAS 03/2023 - PRESENT

CODING BOOT CAMP CERTIFICATE EXPECTED COMPLETION DATE: SEPTEMBER 2023 GITHUB PAGES USERNAME: AFRAZIER01

UNIVERSITY OF KANSAS 08/2022 - PRESENT

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE INFORMATION SYSTEMS EXPECTED GRADUATION DATE: DECEMBER 2023

GPA: 3.72

RELEVANT COURSEWORK:

FUNDAMENTALS OF SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT, FUNDAMENTALS OF BUSINESS COMPUTER NETWORKING, DATABASE MANAGEMENT SYSTEMS, SYSTEMS ANALYSIS AND DESIGN, IT PROJECT MANAGEMENT, INFORMATION SECURITY, CONTEMPORARY INFO TECH TOPICS, FOUNDATIONS BUSINESS ANALYTICS, SPREADSHEET AND DATABASE APPLICATIONS, BUSINESS WRITING

JOHNSON COUNTY COMMUNITY COLLEGE

ASSOCIATE OF SCIENCE GENERAL SCIENCES

GPA: 3.5

UNIVERSITY OF CONNECTICUT 01/2019 - 05/2020

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE CIVIL ENGINEERING GPA: 3.5

RELEVANT COURSEWORK:

INTRO TO COMPUTING FOR ENGINEERS

MILITARY EXPERIENCE

UNITED STATES AIR FORCE 12/2017 - 02/2022

AFSC - 3E651

Honorably discharged on February 16, 2022

LAWRENCE, KS

LAWRENCE, KS

COMPLETION DATE: 06/2022

OVERLAND PARK, KS

STORRS, CT

CONNECTICUT AIR NATIONAL GUARD

OPERATIONS MANAGER, CIVIL ENGINEERING SOUADRON

12/2017 - 06/2020

EAST GRANBY, CT

- Established and managed the operation of the command-and-control center
- · Prepared and managed work requirements during approval, processing, and completion stages of work
- Monitored work costs up to \$10,000 for personal approval to ensure compliance within Air Force limits
- Developed and established operation and maintenance procedures to ensure maximum efficiency
- Reviewed all Air Force Instruction to ensure our office's compliance with the regulations

WORK EXPERIENCE

T-MOBILE 05/2022 – 03/2023

HOME INTERNET EXPERT/TELESALES HOURS WORKED PER WEEK: 37

OVERLAND PARK, KS

- Served existing and prospective customers, while providing a best-in-class customer experience and building loyalty
 - Consistently leveraged digital tools in interactions and onboarding
 - · Completed training on T-Mobile virtual retail experience, new skills, and processes, knowledge of systems and reference resources
 - Consistently sought out information between customers, while also learning about innovations in wireless and technology
 - Completed daily sales meetings to set goals and review any new strategic moves made by the organization

UCONN FACILITY OPERATIONS

CALL CENTER STUDENT STAFF

03/2019 - 06/2020

STORRS, CT

HOURS WORKED PER WEEK: 20

- Managed the operations of all UConn facilities 600+ and building services
- Coordinated with customers, managers, and technicians in case of miscommunication and/or follow-up work
- Processed 20-40 work orders a day to fix/improve facilities

INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE

U.S. DEPARTMENT OF LABOR

05/2023 - PRESENT

KANSAS CITY, MO

EMPLOYEE BENEFITS INVESTIGATOR HOURS WORK PER WEEK: 32

- Review and analyze multiple types of documents and reports of investigation for legal and evidentiary sufficiency and conformity with national enforcement policy.
- Research policy, program issues, and questions that have been raised. Search for and identify relevant court cases, precedents and opinions, and other cases.
- Participate in conducting investigations, including analysis, and gathering of evidence and use of investigative techniques.
- · Review and provide comments on proposed operating plans, identifying legal or administrative issues.
- Conducting research, collecting and developing data reports on enforcement program, administrative operations, and accomplishments
 of the office.

PRUDENTIAL FINANCIAL INC.

07/2019 - 08/2019

HARTFORD, CT

SUMMER FINANCE INTERN, EXPENSE PLANNING&ANALYSIS TEAM HOURS WORKED PER WEEK: 35

- Searched and pulled quarterly detailed expense reports that were composed of over \$900 million of expenses
- Identified difference in thousands/millions in 2018 actual expenses vs present 6-month actuals and differences in 2nd quarter forecast as opposed to the full-year plan
- Updated PowerPoints used for clients for end-of-the-quarter reporting or forecasting

SKILLS

JOB-RELATED SKILLS

- MICROSOFT OFFICE, TEAMWORK
- COMMUNICATION
- ANALYTICAL SKILLS
- SALES
- SOFTWARE DESIGN

LICENSES/CERTIFCATIONS

- PRIVATE PILOT LICENSE
- LINKEDIN DATA SCIENCE FOUNDATIONS
- PCEP CERTIFIED ENTRY_LEVEL PYTHON PROGRAMMER

COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT

•	U. S. AIR FORCE ACADEMY EARLY PATH TO WINGS PROGRAM CONTRIBUTOR	2020 - 2021
•	CHARLIE SQ. ACADEMIC OFFICER	2021 - 2021
•	NUTMEG BIG BROTHERS BIG SISTERS PROGRAM	2019 - 2020
•	UNITED STATES NAVAL SEA CADET CORPS	2016 - 2018
•	NHS PEER MENTORING PROGRAM	2016 - 2018

LEADERSHIP/AWARDS

- UNITED STATES AIR FORCE ACADEMY CONGRESSIONAL NOMINEE
 - O SENATOR CHRIS MURPHY AIR FORCE
 - O CONGRESSMAN JOHN LARSON AIR FORCE
- OPERATIONS MANAGEMENT APPRENTICESHIP SUPERIOR PERFORMER
- AIR FORCE BASIC MILITARY TRAINING HONOR GRADUATE
- AIR FORCE BASIC MILITARY TRAINING HONOR GRADUATE
- EARLY PATH TO WINGS SCHOLARSHIP RECIPIENT/GRADUATE
- NEWINGTON HIGH SCHOOL BUSINESS ACADEMY STUDENT AWARD 2018